Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS.180
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIX: Sound recordings, 192706
  - Series XIX, Subseries A: Sound recordings, 192707
    - Houston, Scott - Phone Message, 4/12/97; 192885 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0162, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0162)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 10 min.
      Scope and Contents
      Content consists of an answering machine message and a phone conversation(s).
    - Houston, Scott; Hall, Julie Ann, 2/27/97; 192884 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0163, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0163)
    - Howard, Richard, 3/14/97; 192883 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0164, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0164)
    - Hawarth, Richard - Square Books, Oxford, Miss, 4/12/97; 192882 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0165, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0165)
    - Jeanette III, Oct. 8, 1996; 192881 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0166, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0166)
    - Jeanette (4), Undated; 192880 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0167, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0167)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 26 min.
    - Jeanette - bits, 5/5/97; 192879 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0168, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0168)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 12 min.
    - Jeanette at Books & Co., 1/14/97; 192878 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0169, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0169)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 49 min., Preservation Note: Noticeable pitch/speed changes in the original recording.
    - Jeanette - scrapbooks, 5/16/97; 192877 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0170, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0170)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 83 min.
    - Jeanette - scrapbooks, 5/12/97; 192876 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0171, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0171)
    - Jeanette - scrapbooks, 5/22/97; 192875 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0172, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0172)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 56 min.
    - Jeanette Sept 30, 192874 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0173, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0173)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 85 min.
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/18/97; 192873 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0174, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0174)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 95 min., Preservation Note: Audio is muted.
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/18/97; 192872 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0175, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0175)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 75 min.
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/19/97; 192871 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0176, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0176)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 58 min.
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/20/97; 192870 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0177, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0177)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 52 min.
    - K., Richie, Undated; 192869 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0178, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0178)
    - Kaplan, Max V., 4/4/97; 192868 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0179, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0179)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 73 min.
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 12/11/96; 192867 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0180, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0180)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 44 min.
    - Leibowitz, Fran, 12/11/96; 192866 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0181, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0181)
    - Lyons, Donald, Undated; 192865 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0182, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0182)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 93 min.
    - McClatchy, JD, 5/19/97; 192864 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0183, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0183)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 7 min.
    - Mead, Taylor, Undated; 192863 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0184, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0184)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 57 min. Preservation Note: Some electronic interference in the original recording.
    - Moonen, Ted, 6/8/97; 192862 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0185, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0185)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 20 min.
    - Moreau, Jeanne, 4/16/97; 192861 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0186, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0186)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 7 min., Preservation Note: Original recording mostly inaudible due to bad phone connection.
    - Moreau, Jeanne - NY1, Channel 4 news, Undated; 192860 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0187, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0187)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 11 min.
      Jeanne Moreau content is in French.
    - Morris, Debi - Barbara's Bookstore; Kaplan, Mitchell - Books and Books, 4/17/97; 192859; Technical problems with original recording yeilded less than 1 minute of content for access CD track 1. (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0188, Case 180.0188)
      Duration: 33 minutes
    - Murray, Albert, 12/6/96; 192858 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0189, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0189)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 62 min.
    - O'Brien, Edna, May 15, 1997; 192857 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0190, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0190)
    - Phillbrook, Peter, 11/11/96; 192856 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0191, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0191)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 72 min.
    - Phillbrook, 12/10/96; 192855 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0192, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0192)
    - Phillbrook, Peter, 3/21/97; 192854 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0193, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0193)
    - Pomeranz, Bud, 1/21/97; 192853 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0194, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0194)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 53 min.
    - Powell, Michael, 4/30/97; 192852 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0195, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0195)
    - Rabinowitz, John, 12/2/96; 192851 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0196, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0196)
    - Ross, David, 11/5/97; 192850 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0197, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0197)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 49 min.
    - Sanger, Alex, 4/14/97; 192849 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0198, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0198)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 65 min.
    - Sanger, Alex, 5/1/97; 192848 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0199, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0199)
    - Schama, Simm, 5/5/98; 192847 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0200, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0200)
    - Schenk, Ginette; Tillman, Lynne; Stockholder, Jessica, 3/26/95; 192846 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0201, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0201)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 94 min.
    - Scott, Susan, Undated; 192845 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0202, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0202)
    - Silverberg, Ira, 2/10/97; 192844 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0203, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0203)
    - Slovak, Paul, Undated; 192843 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0204, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0204)
    - Slovak, Paul, Undated; 192842 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0205, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0205)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 9 min.
    - Solowitz, Ed, Undated; 192841 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0206, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0206)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 42 min.
    - Sontag, Susan, 4/1/98; 180.0207; 192840 (Box 53, Cassette 180.0207, E-records fales_mss180, E-records 180.0207)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 63 min.
    - Spivey, Alexandra Anderson, 3/5/97; 192839 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0208, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0208)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 47 min.
    - Trillin, Calvin, 1/28/97; 192838 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0209, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0209)
    - Trillin, Calvin, 6/29/97; 192837 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0210, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0210)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 16 min.
    - Unowsky, David - Hungry Mind Bookstore, 4/30/97; 192836 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0211, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0211)
    - Varni, Steven, 3/6/97; 192835 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0212, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0212)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 66 min.
    - Varni, Steven - on Whitney, 6/5/97; 192834 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0213, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0213)
    - Watson, Jeanette, 9/20/96; 192833 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0214, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0214)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 86 min., Preservation Note: Mechanical tape-recorder noise heard throughout original recording.
    - Watson, Jeanette - signed books, 4/18/97; 192832 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0215, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0215)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 45 min.
    - Watson, Olive, 4/24/97; 192831 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0216, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0216)
    - Weld, Jackie, 1/14/97; 192830 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0217, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0217)
    - Wilentz, Ted, Undated; 192829 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0218, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0218)
    - Wilson, Martha, 3/24/97; 192828 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0219, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0219)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 34 min.
    - Yau, John, 2/12/97; 192827 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0220, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0220)
    - Yamizaki, Paul - City Lights Bookstore, 5/1/97; 192826 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0221, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0221)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 29 min.
    - Allen, Woody and A. Shaw, Undated; 192825 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0222, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0222)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 76 min, Preservation Note: Sound quality is poor.
    - Ans. Machine - Patrick and Colm on No Lease on Life; Ira singing Happy Birthday; C. Trillin - Jill Goldenberg, 1998; 192824 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0223, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0223)
      Content comprises answering machine messages.
    - Aronowitz, Dec. 7; 192823 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0224, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0224)
    - Aronowitz, Dec. 7; 192822 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0225, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0225)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 59 min.
    - Ashbery, John, Undated; 192821 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0226, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0226)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 14 min.
    - Baldwin, Gordon, Undated; 192820 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0227, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0227)
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/14/86; 192819 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0228, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0228)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 88 min.
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/15/86; 192818 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0229, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0229)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 76 min.
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/17/86; 192817 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0230, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0230)
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/18/86; 192816 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0231, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0231)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 87 min.
    - BBC Radio 4 - Open Book, 24/05/98; 192815 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0232, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0232)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 32 min.
    - Bensman - Chinese Literature, Nov. 15; 192814 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0233, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0233)
    - Bensman and Lynne Tillman, Nov. 15; 192813 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0234, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0234)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 36 min., Preservation Note: Recording contains low mechanical background noise throughout.
    - Bensman and Lynne Tillman - Chinese Literature, Nov. 15; 192812 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0235, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0235)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 94 min., Preservation Note: Recording contains low mechanical background noise throughout.
    - Books & Co. on WNYC, 10/6/99; 192811 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0236, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0236)
    - Book Show #507, 3/31/98; 192810 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0237, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0237)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 25 min.
    - Bookworm, 4/24/91; 192809 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0238, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0238)
    - Bookworm recorded, 3/3/98; 192808 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0239, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0239)
    - Bookworm recorded, 3/3/03; 192807 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0240, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0240)
    - Bookworm - Lynne Tillman, 06/05/03; 192806 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0241, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0241)
    - Bottomly, Susan, Undated; 192805 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0242, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0242)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 23 min., Preservation Note: Recording contains periodic "beep" throughout.
    - Brandauer, Klaus Maria, Undated; 192804 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0243, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0243)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 64 min., Preservation Note: Recording contains reoccurring tape speed changes throughout.
    - Brown class, 4/3/90; 192803 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0244, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0244)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 97 min.
    - Brown, M., 4/24/90; 192802 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0245, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0245)
    - Brown, 4/24/30; 192801 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0246, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0246)
    - Brown, Mike, 4/17/90; 192800 (Box 35, Cassette ID: 180.0247, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0247)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 118 min.
    - Brown, Mike, 5/8/90; 192799 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0248, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0248)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 116 min.
    - Brown, Mike, 5/1/90; 192798 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0249, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0249)
    - Buhl, Henry, Dec. 14, 1999; 192797 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0250, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0250)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 40 min., Preservation Note: Speed of original recording has been digitally corrected.
    - Cale, John, 12/3/93; 192796 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0251, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0251)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 74 min.
    - Cale, John; Tillman, Lynne, Undated; 192795 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0252, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0252)
    - Canada Radio, March 10; 192794 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0253, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0253)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 4 min.
      Content is four minutes of country music.
    - Commodity Group, 1/4/90; 192793 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0254, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0254)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 95 min., Preservation Note: Noticeable speed and start/stop glitches in original recording.
    - Dreher, Peter; Tillman, Lynne, Undated; 192792 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0255, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0255)
    - Fields, Danny, Undated; 192791 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0256, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0256)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 48 min.
    - Fields, Danny - New Xerox, Undated; 192790 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0257, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0257)
    - Ford, C.H., 3/4/90; 192789 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0258, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0258)
    - Ford, C.H. - int. Dakota, Jan. 2001; 192788 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0259, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0259)
    - Foreman, Amanda - Elle (NT), 1999; 192787 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0260, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0260)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 52 min., Preservation Note: Some drop-outs in original recording.
    - Forman - Acker: RF, Undated; 192786 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0261, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0261)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 13 min., Preservation Note: Original recording contains some minor electronic interference.
      First part of content is a "final draft"; second part of content is a "rough draft" of the same information as the first.
    - Geldzahler, Henry, 12/7/92; 192785 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0262, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0262)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 43 min.
    - Giardinelli, Mempo, 10/10/98; 192784 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0263, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0263)
    - Giardinelli, Mempo, 10/10/98; 192783 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0264, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0264)
    - Green, Sam, Undated; 192782 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0265, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0265)
    - Harris, Les, Undated; 192781 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0266, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0266)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 86 min.
    - Harris, Les, Undated; 192780 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0267, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0267)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 95 min.
      Content is a mixture of classical music and a muffled interview with Les Harris.
    - Haynes, Jim - from Paris, Undated; 192779 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0268, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0268)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 62 min., Preservation Note: Speed of original recording has been digitally corrected, sound quality is poor.
      Content is from an answering machine tape.
    - Hughes, Fred - Tour; Sasha Chermaye[l], Feb. 2000; 192778 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0269, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0269)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 47 min., Preservation Note: Interviews recorded at a low volume.
    - Jeanette telling me that Richard Howard loves me..., 1997; 192777 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0270, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0270)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 2 min.
    - Jessica II, Undated; 192776 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0271, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0271)
    - JS/LT - Julia Scher, Lynne Tillman, Undated; 192775 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0272, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0272)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 90 min.
    - Kahn, Stanya, 12/5/01; 192774 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0273, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0273)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 3 min.
    - Kiernan, Frances, Jan. 3, 2000; 192773 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0274, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0274)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 78 min.
    - Kiki; Lynne Tillman, 9/4/03; 192772 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0275, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0275)
    - Jay, Martin - Lacan and Vision, New School, 10/27/90; 192771 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0276, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0276)
    - Lynne's Reading - Ear Inn, 1978; 192770 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0277, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0277)
    - Lyons, Donald, Undated; 192769 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0278, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0278)
    - M., Gerard, Undated; 192768 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0279, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0279)
    - Mallanga, G., Undated; 192767 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0280, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0280)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 86 min., Preservation Note: Intermittent buzzing sound in parts of the original recording.
    - Marx, Jan. 4, 1990; 192766 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0281, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0281)
    - Mathews, Harry, Undated; 192765 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0282, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0282)
      Content recorded with a voice-activated recorder.
    - Mathews, Harry, Undated; 192764 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0283, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0283)
      Some of the content recorded with a voice-activated recorder.
    - Mekas, Jonas, Undated; 192763 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0284, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0284)
    - MOMA Museum of Modern Art - Kiki Smith, 1/28/04; 192762 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0285, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0285)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 82 min.
    - MOMA Museum of Modern Art - Kiki Smith, 1/28/04; 192761 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0286, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0286)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 84 min., Preservation Note: Speed of original recording has been digitally corrected.
    - Morrissey, Paul, Undated; 192760 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0287, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0287)
    - Morrison, Sterling, Undated; 192759 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0288, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0288)
    - Name, Billy, Undated; 192758 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0289, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0289)
    - Name, Billy, Undated; 192757 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0290, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0290)
    - Night Waves, 22/04/03; 192756 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0291, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0291)
    - No/Yes and Hung Up, Undated; 192755 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0292, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0292)
    - NYELO - Whitney Biennial, 4/5/95; 192754 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0293, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0293)
    - Olender, Bill; Group Material, Undated; 192753 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0294, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0294)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 88 min., Preservation Note: Recording contains reoccurring background mechanical noise.
    - P.A.N. Radio Show: WBAI, 1977; 192752 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0295, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0295)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 56 min., Preservation Note: Sound quality is poor.
      Part of the content is from an answering machine tape; part is a radio show interview.
    - Prina, Stephen - Push Comes to Love, Undated; 192751 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0296)
    - PS1 - Conversation Privacy, Undated; 192750 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0297, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0297)
    - Radio Interview - Lynne Tillman, Leonard Lopate - WNYC, 1/29/98; 192749 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0298, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0298)
    - Radio Show - WFMU, Undated; 192748 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0299, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0299)
    - Rainer, Yvonne, 1991; 192747 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0300, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0300)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 42 min., Preservation Note: Recording contains reoccurring tape speed changes throughout.
    - Renoir, Undated; 192746 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0301, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0301)
    - Rodney, Undated; 192745 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0302, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0302)
    - Rosenberg, Aura, Undated; 192744 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0303, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0303)
    - S., Stephen, Undated; 192743 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0304, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0304)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 95 min., Preservation Note: Noticeable speed changes throughout the recording.
    - Schneebaum, Tobias; Wert, Joel Sanger, 2002; 192742 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0305, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0305)
    - Schneider, Gary, Feb. 22, 04; 192741 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0306, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0306)
    - Shaw, Aiden, Undated; 192740 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0307, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss180_0307)
      Format: Audiocassette, Duration: 57 min., Preservation Note: Sound quality is poor.